{
  "quizInfo": {
    "Subject": "Great Books",
    "Term": "Midterms",
    "Title": "Pride and Prejudice",
    "LastModified": "25 March 2025",
    "Authors": [
      "Alexander Oro"
    ],
    "References": [
      "Pride and Prejudice"
    ]
  },
  "quizData": [
    {
      "question": "How many daughters did Mrs. Bennet have?",
      "answer": "Five",
      "choices": [
        "Three",
        "Four",
        "Six",
        "Five"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is known for their false pride?",
      "answer": "Darcy",
      "choices": [
        "Bingley",
        "Wickham",
        "Mr. Bennet",
        "Darcy"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "What did Lydia do that scandalized her family?",
      "answer": "Ran off with an army officer",
      "choices": [
        "Got married secretly",
        "Became seriously ill",
        "Lost family fortune",
        "Ran off with an army officer"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who was described as too shy to show affection?",
      "answer": "Jane",
      "choices": [
        "Elizabeth",
        "Lydia",
        "Mary",
        "Jane"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who secretly admired Elizabeth despite appearing proud and aloof?",
      "answer": "Darcy",
      "choices": [
        "Wickham",
        "Bingley",
        "Mr. Collins",
        "Darcy"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the officer Lydia ran off with?",
      "answer": "Wickham",
      "choices": [
        "Bingley",
        "Darcy",
        "Mr. Collins",
        "Wickham"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "How many dances did Darcy dance at the first ball?",
      "answer": "Four",
      "choices": [
        "Two",
        "Six",
        "Eight",
        "Four"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who inherited Mr. Bennet's home and estate upon his death?",
      "answer": "Mr. Collins",
      "choices": [
        "Darcy",
        "Bingley",
        "Wickham",
        "Mr. Collins"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who proposed to Elizabeth first but was rejected?",
      "answer": "Mr. Collins",
      "choices": [
        "Bingley",
        "Darcy",
        "Wickham",
        "Mr. Collins"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Who provided financial help to arrange Lydia's marriage?",
      "answer": "Darcy",
      "choices": [
        "Mr. Bennet",
        "Bingley",
        "Mr. Collins",
        "Darcy"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the proper arrangement of the events?",
      "answer": "Bingley moves to Netherfield - Jane visits Netherfield - Darcy insults Elizabeth - Elizabeth visits Charlotte - Lydia elopes",
      "choices": [
        "Darcy insults Elizabeth - Jane visits Netherfield - Bingley moves to Netherfield - Lydia elopes - Elizabeth visits Charlotte",
        "Jane visits Netherfield - Bingley moves to Netherfield - Elizabeth visits Charlotte - Darcy insults Elizabeth - Lydia elopes",
        "Lydia elopes - Elizabeth visits Charlotte - Jane visits Netherfield - Darcy insults Elizabeth - Bingley moves to Netherfield",
        "Bingley moves to Netherfield - Jane visits Netherfield - Darcy insults Elizabeth - Elizabeth visits Charlotte - Lydia elopes"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the proper arrangement of these scenes?",
      "answer": "Mr. Bennet visits Mr. Bingley - The first ball occurs - Jane visits Netherfield - Elizabeth refuses Mr. Collins - Lydia runs away with Wickham",
      "choices": [
        "The first ball occurs - Mr. Bennet visits Mr. Bingley - Lydia runs away with Wickham - Elizabeth refuses Mr. Collins - Jane visits Netherfield",
        "Jane visits Netherfield - Elizabeth refuses Mr. Collins - Mr. Bennet visits Mr. Bingley - Lydia runs away with Wickham - The first ball occurs",
        "Lydia runs away with Wickham - Mr. Bennet visits Mr. Bingley - Elizabeth refuses Mr. Collins - The first ball occurs - Jane visits Netherfield",
        "Mr. Bennet visits Mr. Bingley - The first ball occurs - Jane visits Netherfield - Elizabeth refuses Mr. Collins - Lydia runs away with Wickham"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the correct sequence of these events?",
      "answer": "Darcy insults Elizabeth - Wickham tells Elizabeth his story - Elizabeth refuses Darcy's proposal - Darcy explains truth in a letter",
      "choices": [
        "Wickham tells Elizabeth his story - Elizabeth refuses Darcy's proposal - Darcy insults Elizabeth - Darcy explains truth in a letter",
        "Elizabeth refuses Darcy's proposal - Darcy insults Elizabeth - Wickham tells Elizabeth his story - Darcy explains truth in a letter",
        "Darcy explains truth in a letter - Elizabeth refuses Darcy's proposal - Darcy insults Elizabeth - Wickham tells Elizabeth his story",
        "Darcy insults Elizabeth - Wickham tells Elizabeth his story - Elizabeth refuses Darcy's proposal - Darcy explains truth in a letter"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the proper sequence of these scenes?",
      "answer": "Lydia runs away - Mr. Gardiner finds Lydia - Lydia marries Wickham - Darcy visits Elizabeth at home - Elizabeth and Darcy get engaged",
      "choices": [
        "Darcy visits Elizabeth at home - Lydia runs away - Lydia marries Wickham - Mr. Gardiner finds Lydia - Elizabeth and Darcy get engaged",
        "Lydia marries Wickham - Lydia runs away - Mr. Gardiner finds Lydia - Darcy visits Elizabeth at home - Elizabeth and Darcy get engaged",
        "Elizabeth and Darcy get engaged - Darcy visits Elizabeth at home - Lydia runs away - Lydia marries Wickham - Mr. Gardiner finds Lydia",
        "Lydia runs away - Mr. Gardiner finds Lydia - Lydia marries Wickham - Darcy visits Elizabeth at home - Elizabeth and Darcy get engaged"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    },
    {
      "question": "Which is the proper order of events involving Elizabeth and Darcy?",
      "answer": "Elizabeth overhears Darcy insult her - Elizabeth refuses to dance with Darcy - Darcy proposes marriage - Elizabeth rejects Darcy's proposal - Darcy helps Lydia marry Wickham",
      "choices": [
        "Elizabeth refuses to dance with Darcy - Darcy proposes marriage - Elizabeth overhears Darcy insult her - Darcy helps Lydia marry Wickham - Elizabeth rejects Darcy's proposal",
        "Darcy proposes marriage - Elizabeth overhears Darcy insult her - Elizabeth refuses to dance with Darcy - Elizabeth rejects Darcy's proposal - Darcy helps Lydia marry Wickham",
        "Elizabeth rejects Darcy's proposal - Elizabeth overhears Darcy insult her - Darcy proposes marriage - Darcy helps Lydia marry Wickham - Elizabeth refuses to dance with Darcy",
        "Elizabeth overhears Darcy insult her - Elizabeth refuses to dance with Darcy - Darcy proposes marriage - Elizabeth rejects Darcy's proposal - Darcy helps Lydia marry Wickham"
      ],
      "reference": "Pride and Prejudice",
      "term": "Midterms"
    }
  ]
}